One common mistake that beginning
developers often make, is that they start
to think about how to make money from an
app, only after they're done building it.
In contrast, more successful
developers think deeply about how to
make money from their apps,
right from the start.
That is, they design their apps with
a modidization model already in mind.
In this guest lecture, we have experts
from the Amazon app store team,
who will share with us some
initial thoughts on how to
successfully monetize your Android apps.
So, please click on this link, and
see what they have to say on an issue
that's unarguably important to many,
if not most, professional app developers.